<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tue Hellstern :: Kea</title>
    <link>http://example.org/5.-Semester/Know-Your-Data/etl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tue Hellstern :: Kea</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/5.-Semester/Know-Your-Data/etl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/5.-Semester/Know-Your-Data/etl/automate-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/5.-Semester/Know-Your-Data/etl/automate-excel/</guid>
      <description>Automate data processing#In Excel using Python, Pandas, and Openpyxl#Files#Excel
sales_data.xlsx sales_data.xlsx Jupyter Lab
Real_world_example.ipynb demo.ipynb openpyxl-chart-notebook.ipynb openpyxl-tutorial.ipynb Introduction#This is all about automating Microsoft Excel using python and two different libraries.
The first library is Pandas. This library is used to process dataframes at high speed. Pandas is used all over the world of data analysis, data science, and data engineering. A basic workflow is Pandas is to load and excel file into a dataframe, apply all sorts of complex processing wit few lines of code, then save the results into Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/5.-Semester/Know-Your-Data/etl/excel-powerbi-etl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/5.-Semester/Know-Your-Data/etl/excel-powerbi-etl/</guid>
      <description>Home
Excel and ETL#Excel and Power BI has a powerful data analysis pack named Get and Transform (previously known as Power Query).
It is an ETL pack for cleaning and sorting raw data from a range of input sources, such as CSV and text files.
In this age of data lakes and petabyte-scale databases, it is shocking how frequently you still receive data in the form of CSV, text, and Excel files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETL</title>
      <link>http://example.org/5.-Semester/Know-Your-Data/etl/slides/ETL-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/5.-Semester/Know-Your-Data/etl/slides/ETL-slide/</guid>
      <description>ETL #Extract - Transform - Load #Data sources #Can you name some data sources? #Why ETL?#Analyze business data for taking critical business decisions Transactional databases cannot answer complex business questions Provides a method of moving the data from various sources into a data warehouse Allow verification of data transformation, aggregation and calculations rules ETL process can perform complex transformations ETL helps to Migrate data into a Data Warehouse Tools #Can you name some ETL tools?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
